(Leonard:)Sandwich shop.
(Leonard:)Doesn't that violate
the health code or...?
(Penny:)No, at the sub shop,
we were only making out.
Ah, okay.
(Leonard:)But my point is that you have absolutely
no reason to be embarrassed.
Really? Do you think I overreacted?
- Maybe a little.
- Because I do that, I do overreact.
- Maybe I should call Mike and apologize.
- No, no.
No, that would be under-reacting.
(Leonard:)He did break the implied confidentiality
of the bedroom...
(Leonard:)...and in your case, the elevator,
parks and fast-food franchise.
(Penny:)Yes, you're right.
I should just say I am done with him.
(Leonard:)Yes you should. Go ahead, say it.
(Penny:)But I never gave the man a chance
to explain.
What is there to explain?
It's all right here.
It's betrayal.
(Penny:)No, you were right the first time.
(Penny:)This is a man who loves me...
...but in his own stupid way was just trying
to show people how he feels.